Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Phonograph records
  - Shostakovich: Symphony No. 8 (Parts 1 and 3), 04/1944; bell_brothers_137; lacquer on glass disc
  - Shostakovich: Symphony No. 8 (Parts 2 and 4), 04/1944; bell_brothers_138; lacquer on glass disc
  - Showtime (No. 125-126), undated; bell_brothers_477; vinyl disc
  - Sibelius: Tapiola, Boston Symphony Orchestra, Koussevitzky (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_247; shellac disc
  - Sibelius: Tapiola, Boston Symphony Orchestra, Koussevitzky (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_248; shellac disc
  - Sibelius: Tapiola, Boston Symphony Orchestra, Koussevitzky (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_272; shellac disc
  - Sibelius: Tapiola, Boston Symphony Orchestra, Koussevitzky (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_139; shellac disc
  - Sibelius: The Swan of Tuonela, Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra (Part 1), 03/27/1940; bell_brothers_270; shellac disc
  - Sibelius: The Swan of Tuonela, Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra (Part 2), 03/27/1940; bell_brothers_271; shellac disc
  - Sky Over Britain, guest Violet Heming; guest Helen Hayes (No. 5-6), 11/05/1941; bell_brothers_253; vinyl disc
  - Social Security Spot Announcements: The New Social Security Law, undated; bell_brothers_692; vinyl disc
  - Something for the Girls: Sammy Kaye's Serenade; American Album of Familiar Music (Series 2, No. 3-4), undated; bell_brothers_493; vinyl disc
  - Soprano in Italiano: Gaetano Donizetti - Linda di Chamounix, Atto 1: O Luce di quest, Florence Macbeth; Ruggero Leoncavallo - Zazà, Atto 3, Mamma Vicina di Casa, Geraldine Farrar, undated; bell_brothers_118; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Sound Off (No. 13, parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_505; vinyl disc
  - Speech on Potsdam, undated; bell_brothers_104; lacquer on glass disc
  - Spohr: Symphony No. 2 in D Minor, Op. 49 (Parts 1 and 3), 08/14/1941; bell_brothers_190; lacquer on glass disc
  - Spohr: Symphony No. 2 in D Minor, Op. 49 (Parts 2 and 4), 08/14/1941; bell_brothers_191; lacquer on glass disc
  - Spohr: Symphony No. 2 in D Minor, Op. 49 (Parts 5 and 7), 08/14/1941; bell_brothers_162; lacquer on glass disc
  - Spotlight Bands (No. 539-540), 12/07/1944; 12/08/1944; bell_brothers_490; vinyl disc
  - Stand by for Music: Bell Sisters with Frank De Vol and his Orchestra; Jeff Chandler with Frank De Vol and his Orchestra (No. 9-10), undated; bell_brothers_631; vinyl disc
  - Stars on Parade: Swing and Sway with Sammy Kaye; One for the Money with Cornel Wilde (No. 547-548), 02/22/1951; 03/30/1951; 03/01/1951; 04/06/1951; bell_brothers_629; vinyl disc
  - Stoessel: Garrick, (Part 2); Poulenc: Trio For Horn, Trumpet, and Trombone, undated; bell_brothers_156; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Stokowski, Philadelphia Orchestra: Pictures at an Exhibition (Part 8), 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_140; on shellac disc
  - Sunday Serenade, Sammy Kaye (No. 96), 04/08/1945; bell_brothers_516; vinyl disc
  - Sunday Serenade, Sammy Kaye (No. 101), 05/12/1945; bell_brothers_609; vinyl disc
  - Sunday Serenade, Sammy Kaye (No. 102), 05/20/1945; bell_brothers_517; vinyl disc
  - Ténor et Basse en Francais: Giacomo Meyerbeer - Robert le diable, Acte 3 - Du rendez-vous, Edmond Clement, Marcel Journet; Giacomo Meyerbeer - Robert le diable, Acte 1, undated; bell_brothers_1033; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: A String of Pearls; The Breeze is My Sweetheart, undated; bell_brothers_106; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Don't You Know I Care; Kalamazoo [sic], undated; bell_brothers_089; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Dreamer; Tonight, undated; bell_brothers_088; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: I am in the Mood for Love; Blues in My Heart, undated; bell_brothers_112; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: I Still Get a Thrill; Count Every Star, undated; bell_brothers_108; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: I‘ve Got a Heart Full with Love; Adios, undated; bell_brothers_107; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: I’ll Always Love You; Tenderly, undated; bell_brothers_090; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Largo; Blue Rain, undated; bell_brothers_109; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Little Brown Jug; Somebody Loves Me, undated; "bell_brothers_087 "; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Pennsylvania 6-5000; Always, undated; "bell_brothers_085 "; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Serenade in Blue; Tuxedo Junction, undated; bell_brothers_110; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: That Old Black Magic; My Buddy, undated; bell_brothers_111; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Tex Beneke: Your Eye; La Rosita, undated; bell_brothers_086; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Caine Mutiny Court-Martial (Part 1), 11/19/1955; bell_brothers_440; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Caine Mutiny Court-Martial (Part 2), 11/19/1955; bell_brothers_441; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Caine Mutiny Court-Martial (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_232; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Catholic Hour: Monsignor Sheelan, 03/05/1944; bell_brothers_218; lacquer on glass disc
  - The Chocolate Soldier (Parts 1 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_060; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Chocolate Soldier (Parts 2 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_061; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Fight for a Jewish Army, 06/11/1942; bell_brothers_492; plastic disc
  - The Hydrogen Bomb and the Peril to Mankind; Racing with Time, 12/22/1954; 12/23/1954; bell_brothers_789; vitrolac disc
  - The Master’s Music Room (No. 13A-13B), undated; bell_brothers_025; shellac disc
  - The National Guard Show: Mindy Carson and Red Barber (No. 41-42), 11/02/1951; 11/09/1951; bell_brothers_578; vinyl disc
  - The National Guard Show: Mindy Carson and Red Barber (No. 43-44), 11/16/1951; 11/23/1951; bell_brothers_500; vinyl disc
  - The Ramblers; The Flamingos; The Swallows; The Coronets, Sax Mallard Combo; The Ambassadors; The Castelles, undated; bell_brothers_074; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Shadow (Lilly Theater of the Air, Part 1); Orchestra: Three Waltz and Movements Musicals by Schubert (Part 2), 03/15/1944; bell_brothers_205; lacquer on glass disc
  - The Shadow (Lilly Theater of the Air, no part identifier); Orchestra: Three Waltz and Movements Musicals by Schubert (Part 1), 03/15/1944; bell_brothers_204; lacquer on glass disc
  - The Shape of Darkness (with Sir Cedric Hardwick and Edward Begley); Larry Adler - Harmonica with Orchestra Ravel’s Bolero, 03/19/1944; bell_brothers_206; lacquer on glass disc
  - The Spirit of the Vikings: Joseph Auslander reads his poem, To the Unconquerable Norwegians (No. 2540); Norway Fights On, Battle in the Arctic, a drama (No. 2541), undated; bell_brothers_637; vinyl disc
  - The Spirit of the Vikings: Norway and the World Today, Talk by the Honorable Finn Moe, Member of Parliament; Norwegian Christmas Program, Narrator: Gladys M. Petch (No. 2851), undated; bell_brothers_638; vinyl disc
  - The Spirit of the Vikings: Norwegian Marches, played by Oslo Military Band (No. 2847); Siljuslaatten by Harald Seeverud, played by Oslo Philharmonic Orchestra, Odd Gruner-Hegge, conductor (No 2848), undated; bell_brothers_639; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episodes 7-8), undated; bell_brothers_760; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 41-42), undated; bell_brothers_761; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 43-44), undated; bell_brothers_762; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 51-52), undated; bell_brothers_763; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 57-58), undated; bell_brothers_764; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 65-66), undated; bell_brothers_765; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 67-68), undated; bell_brothers_766; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 71-72), undated; bell_brothers_767; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 85-86), undated; bell_brothers_768; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 87-88), undated; bell_brothers_769; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 89-90), undated; bell_brothers_770; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 91-92), undated; bell_brothers_771; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 95-96), undated; bell_brothers_772; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 105-106), undated; bell_brothers_773; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 107-108), undated; bell_brothers_774; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 125-126), undated; bell_brothers_775; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 127-128), undated; bell_brothers_776; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 131-132), undated; bell_brothers_777; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 151-152), undated; bell_brothers_778; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 169-170), undated; bell_brothers_779; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 175-176), undated; bell_brothers_780; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 187-188), undated; bell_brothers_781; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 233-234), undated; bell_brothers_782; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 239-240), undated; bell_brothers_783; vinyl disc
  - The Story of Ruby Valentine starring Juanita Hall (Episode 253-254), undated; bell_brothers_784; vinyl disc
  - The Vibranaires: Ooh, I Feel So Good; Stop Jiving Baby, undated; bell_brothers_115; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - The Voice of Information and Education: G. I. Jive (Series H-12, No. 1763-1764), 02/04/1945; bell_brothers_529; vinyl disc
  - The Voice of Information and Education: Just Jazz (Series H-83, No. 21), undated; bell_brothers_506; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: 7th, Sing for the Seventh; Music for Millions featuring Frank Parker and Nick and Charles Kenny with Mark Warnow's Orchestra (No. 21), 06/29/1945; bell_brothers_640; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: Betty Madigan with Del Sharbutt and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra; Jo Stafford with John Conte and Paul Weston and His Orchestra (No. 517-518), 02/17/1957; 02/24/1957; bell_brothers_645; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: Edward G. Robinson with John Conte and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra; Ella Logan with Del Sharbutt and George Greeley and His Orchestra (No. 405-406), 12/26/1954; 01/02/1955; bell_brothers_642; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: Guest Star No. 537: Rise Stevens with Del Sharbutt and Mitchell Ayers and His Orchestra; The Four Lads with Del Sharbutt and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra (No. 537-538), 07/07/1957; 07/14/1957; bell_brothers_646; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: Joni James with John Conte and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra; Ida Lupino in Fear with John Conte and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra (No. 331-332), 07/26/1953; 08/02/1953; 09/02/1953; 09/09/1953; bell_brothers_641; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: Sammy Davis, Jr. with Harry Von Zell and Sonny Burke and His Orchestra; Polly Bergen with John Conte and Harry Sosnik and the Savings Bonds Orchestra (No. 453-454), 11/27/1955; 12/04/1955; bell_brothers_643; vinyl disc
  - Treasury Department Radio Recording: The Boston Pops Orchestra with Ben Grauer; Count Basie and His Orchestra with John Conte (No. 457-458), 12/25/1955; 01/01/1956; 02/03/1956; 04/11/1956; bell_brothers_644; vinyl disc
  - Variations on Theme by Haydn (Brahms): Variations 1 and 2, Part 1, Luboshutz and Nemenoff (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_350; vitrolac disc
  - Variations on Theme by Haydn (Brahms): Variations 1 and 2, Part 2, Luboshutz and Nemenoff, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_351; vitrolac disc
  - Variations on Theme by Haydn (Brahms): Variations 7, Luboshutz and Nemenoff, (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_352; vitrolac disc
  - Variations on Theme by Haydn (Saint-Saëns): Finale, Luboshutz and Nemenoff, (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_353; vitrolac disc
  - Verdi: Il Trovatore, Rosa Raisa, Ms. Capps, Staller, 08/04/1921; 08/16/1943; bell_brothers_409; shellac disc
  - Village Store (No. 58), 10/26/1944; bell_brothers_575; vinyl disc
  - Villa-Lobos: Cancao do Carreiro, Elsie Houston, undated; bell_brothers_427; shellac disc
  - Villa-Lobos: Quatuor for Harp, Elsie Houston with Women Chorus (Part 1), 10/26/1940; bell_brothers_425; shellac disc
  - Villa-Lobos: Quatuor for Harp, Elsie Houston with Women Chorus (Part 2), 10/26/1940; bell_brothers_426; shellac disc
  - Voice of the Army: Listen to Your Heart; One of the Best (No. 178-179), undated; bell_brothers_627; vinyl disc
  - Voice of the Army: Sing for your lady starring Bobby Breen; Battering Ram starring Jean Parker (No. 389-390), 01/20/1948; 01/22/1948; bell_brothers_628; vinyl disc
  - Von Dittersdorf: Concerto for Cembalo and Orchestra (Parts 2 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_212; lacquer on glass disc
  - Von Dittersdorf: Concerto for Cembalo and Orchestra (Part 5); Dvorak: Overture - Benvenuto Cellin (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_213; lacquer on glass disc
  - Wallingford Riegger: New Dance, undated; bell_brothers_281; on vitrolac disc
  - Walter Winchell talks on a charge by the Dies in America activities and gives War News (Part 1); Borrah Minevitch and His Harmonica Rascals (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_216; lacquer on glass disc
  - Waltz Time (No. 105), 10/05/1945; bell_brothers_518; vinyl disc
  - Waltz Time, Frank Munn (No. 83), 05/04/1945; bell_brothers_514; vinyl disc
  - War, undated; "bell_brothers_081 "; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - War of the World, Orson Wells (Parts 1 and 2), 10/30/1937; bell_brothers_443; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - War of the World, Orson Wells (Parts 3 and 4), 10/30/1937; bell_brothers_444; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - WCAU: Mike Mystery, undated; bell_brothers_037; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - We the People: Message from a pres. For the War Benefit; Admiral Sherman (captain of the old Carrier Lexington), undated; bell_brothers_217; lacquer on glass disc
  - West Coast and Pearl Harbor Navy Yard Recruiting Spot Announcements, undated; bell_brothers_633; vinyl disc
  - Wil Smith, undated; bell_brothers_246; lacquer on glass disc
  - Will Oakland, undated; bell_brothers_141; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Xavier Cugat Show (No. 20), undated; bell_brothers_479; vinyl disc
  - Yarns for Yanks, William Gargan: Blood Pressure; John Nesbitt: Stories From the Passing Parade (Series H-13, No. 45-46, undated; bell_brothers_613; vinyl disc
  - Your Star Time, starring Lina Romay with Buzz Adlam and His Orchestra, Hy Averback - announcer (No. 17-18), undated; bell_brothers_632; vinyl disc
  - Zenobia, Cast: Oliver Hardy; Billie Burke; Harry Langdon; Alice Brady, undated; bell_brothers_036; vinyl disc
  - [Untitled], undated; bell_brothers_099; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [Untitled], undated; bell_brothers_100; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [untitled], undated; bell_brothers_070; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [Untitled], undated; bell_brothers_073; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [Untitled], undated; bell_brothers_230; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [Untitled], undated; bell_brothers_231; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - [untitled] (Parts 3 and 4), 01/13/1940; bell_brothers_737; lacquer on aluminum disc
- Audiotapes
  - 12th Night (BBC) - (Shakespeare) - Concerto (Busconi) - Night Flight (Dallapiccola) -Carter - Skalkottas- Dallapiccola- Schuller, 05/23/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_425; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - 42 St. Recital; Footlight Parade; V. Spivey; McGuire Sisters; Miscellaneous Vocal singers; Mathis Der Maler, 11/02/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_544; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - A bedtime story, Maurice Chevalier, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_089; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 7)
  - A Taste of Fresh Air, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_255; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - A Taste of Fresh Air WBAI, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_693; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - A Taste of Fresh Air WBAI, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_694; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Academy Awards, 04/17/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_247; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Adriadne Auf Naxos (R. Strauss) Maria Jeritza - Lotte Lehmann, 02/02/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_661; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Adriana Lecouveur (Cilea) - Busoni - Tourel- Oboukhova- Cuenod- Menuhin- Town Hall Meeting of the Air, 05/30/1935; bell_brothers_tapes_293; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Adriana Lecouvreur (Cilea) - Dr. R. Barker - Faust (Schumann) E. Soderstrom, Sop. - Edison Cylinders, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_640; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - After the Ball; Admiral. Rickover; Ethel Waters (TV); Stoaway; Temple Moscow Recital; Churchill; F. Ye end, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_508; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Aida Metropolitan Thrill of Brazil (Tito Guizar) - Grace Moore Biog. Loves of Carmen; (R.H.), 03/03/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_364; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Air Adventures; Ariadne Auf Naxos; Turandot, Busoni: Cabeza de Vaca, Antheil; Pins and Needles, Rome; Rakes Progress Stravinsky, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_444; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Al Jolson - Harry Jolson - Eddie Cantor - Sophie Tucker, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_668; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Alan Shephard; Felia Litvinne; Blanche Marchesi; Ellen Beach Yaw; Irene Abendroth; Eichmann Trail; The Rebel Gun, Robert Morse, The Accused, Opera, 05/08/1961; 05/09/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_106; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Albanese and Buitoni; Gurre-Lieder, Schoenberg; Danse Macabre, Wedeking; White House Tour; Duke Ellington, O. Sitwell; Svengali, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_710; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Albanese and Buitoni; Gurre-Lieder, Schoenberg; Danse Macabre, Wedeking; White House Tour; Duke Ellington, O. Sitwell; Svengali, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_711; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Alceste (Gluck) My Gal Sal, 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_273; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Alcestis Gluck Metropolitan, 02/11/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_195; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Alcestis Gluck Metropolitan, 02/11/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_196; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Alcina, Handel, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_180; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - Ali Baba (Cherubini); Portrait of Mano (Massenet); Rebecca (Franck), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_662; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - American Association of Science, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_250; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - American Association of Science Stanley Green, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_249; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Anchors Aweigh - Peter Sellers and Sophia Loren- Kingston Trio- Sports Personalities- Osy Farres Das Marienleben (Hindemith), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_312; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Animal Farm - Woodrow Wilson - Edison Cylinders - La Traviata (Verdi) Metropolitan Anna Moffo; Hound of Heaven (Jacobson), 04/21/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_404; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Anna Christie, Greta Garbo, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_208; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Anna Karenina; Fear; M. Raye; A star is born; Judi Garland; I. Piatigorsky, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_297; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Anthology of Cante Flamenco, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_534; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Applausus (Haydn) Symphony #5 (Mendelssohn)- Jewels Of the Madonna - Fra Gherad o (Pizetti) Germania - Carl Sandburg - Pastorale Childhood of Christ (J.C. Bach), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_361; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - April Love - Oscar Awards - Emilio De Gorgorza - Carl Jung - Luisa Miller - F. Sinatra, 04/08/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_639; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - April Showers, Amelia Earhart; Solomon, Handle; Bell Telephone Hour, Leadbelly, Szent-Gyorgyi; Mama, Gigli, Film, 04/13/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_412; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Arabella R. Strauss; Joselito, 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_149; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Arabella R. Strauss; Joselito, 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_150; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Arch of Triumph E. Hemingway- M. Gandhi- Cleopatra (Beriloz) - Piano Concerto, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_288; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Are you with it; Shocking Miss Pilgrim, Mindru Katz; Rage in heaven; Pli Selon Pli, Boulez; Maria Alex. Mikhailova, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_296; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Ariane Et Barbeblue, Dukas; Como; David Merrick; Robert Morley, TV; Maurice Chevalier, 02/27/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_567; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Armide, Cluck; Platee, Rameau; In the Navy, Film; Winston Churchill; Spring time in Paris, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_389; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Armide, Gluck; Cyrano Di Bergerac, Alfano, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_511; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Ayn Rand; Yuri Gagarin, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_411; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - B. Minor Mass (Bach)) Solomon (Handel) - Richard II- Harnasie (Karol Szymanowski) That Lady in Ermine Film Betty Grable, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_431; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - Babe Ruth - Works by Florent Schmitt - Piano Sonata (Ives) - Masked Ball Metropolitan - A Day at the Circus, 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_271; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Babes in Arms; Haunted Castle, Moniuszko; The Martydom of St. Sebastian, Debussy; The Establishment, Teddy Wilson Trio, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_626; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Balalaika, Eddy; Religious Works, Maria Kurenko; English Songs; Sea Ballads, 02/28/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_379; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Barber Of Seville (Paisiello), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_188; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Barber of Seville (Tagliavini) Film, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_100; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Barber of Seville, Metropolitan, J. Paar, 03/09/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_575; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Bathing Beauty; Perry Como; Traviata; Queen Elizabeth II; Caval. Rusticana; Crosby; Martin Xmas Show, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_542; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Beatrice, Hoiby, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_674; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 49)
  - Beautitudes (Franck) - Boheme Leoncaval, 01/06/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_376; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Beggars Opera Three Penny Op. Omar Khayyam; Die Mutter (Brecht-Eisler) Wins. Churchill; Merchant of Venice (Orson Wells), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_152; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Belgian Festival; Bergen Festival; Toscanini; La Cenerentola (Rossini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_641; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Belgian Festival; Bergen Festival; Craft Music Hall; B. Crosby; Kraft; Crosby; Goodman Concert, 05/21/1942; 05/28/1942; 06/04/1942; 10/04/1942; 11/20/1937; bell_brothers_tapes_609; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Bell Telephone Hour Schubert Program - M. Matzenauer- Alfred E. Smith- Florenz Ziegfeld, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_286; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Belshaz ar; Buck Privates, Stan Kenton, Penelope Bluebeards Castle, Pesebre, 06/22/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_492; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - Ben Gurion; Perry Como; March of Dimes; Land of Pharaohs; This Way Please; So This is Love, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_538; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)